<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>StickLord.com</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/sticklordblog/" />
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/sticklordblog/atom.xml" />
    <id>tag:sticklord.com,2009-04-23:/sticklordblog//2</id>
    <updated>2009-04-27T02:51:15Z</updated>
    
    <generator uri="http://www.sixapart.com/movabletype/">Movable Type Pro 4.23-en</generator>

<entry>
    <title>Final Fentasy</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/sticklordblog/2009/02/final-fentasy.html" />
    <id>tag:sticklord.com,2009:/sticklordblog//2.228</id>

    <published>2009-02-07T05:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2009-04-27T02:51:15Z</updated>

    <summary>With the release of the Clan Lord development tools, Sticktendo is proud to announce this bold re-imagining of the world of Shan Deral. Featuring a host of popular Clan Lord characters and also Hoggle, Final Fentasy is guaranteed to delight!...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Bi-ru the Wonder Hamster</name>
    </author>

    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us" xml:base="/sticklordblog/">
        <![CDATA[<p>With the release of the Clan Lord development tools, Sticktendo is proud to announce this bold re-imagining of the world of Shan Deral. Featuring a host of popular Clan Lord characters and also Hoggle, Final Fentasy is guaranteed to delight!</p>

<p>Witness great moments in Puddleby history:<br />
* Daimoth's arrival in Puddleby<br />
* Daimoth's first vanquish!<br />
* Daimoth's first rank!<br />
* That time Maeght did that thing<br />
* How Daimoth met Lorikeet<br />
* When Cody killed Measle with a well-aimed cross-sn'ell uncharged mega buster blast<br />
* You don't remember that? Seriously, where have you been?</p>

<p>Now with 200% less Zynx!</p>]]>
        
<![CDATA[<p><b><a href="/sticklordblog/2009/02/final-fentasy.html">Check It Out</a></b></p>]]>
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>The Legend of Sylva</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/sticklordblog/2008/08/the-legend-of-sylva.html" />
    <id>tag:sticklord.com,2008:/sticklordblog//2.227</id>

    <published>2008-08-30T02:35:18Z</published>
    <updated>2009-04-27T02:39:18Z</updated>

    <summary>In honor of the 100th anniversary of Zynx&apos;s legendary conquest of Albania, Sticktendo and SL Games present The Legend of Sylva, an edugaming adventure through the life and times of Puddleby&apos;s most compelling hero. The Legend of Sylva covers all...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Bi-ru the Wonder Hamster</name>
    </author>

    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us" xml:base="/sticklordblog/">
        <![CDATA[<p>In honor of the 100th anniversary of Zynx's legendary conquest of Albania, Sticktendo and SL Games present <b>The Legend of Sylva</b>, an edugaming adventure through the life and times of Puddleby's most compelling hero.</p>

<p><b>The Legend of Sylva</b> covers all of Zynx's most fascinating adventures in thrilling 6-bit graphics.  Watch as he defeats the dark wizard Grindelwald!  Help him liberate princess Sylva from the foul clutches of Ralph Nader!  Join him as he secures sainthood by driving all the serpents out of New Jersey!  With <b>The Legend of Sylva</b>, you get to <i>live</i> the adventure!</p>]]>
        
<![CDATA[<p><b><a href="/sticklordblog/2008/08/the-legend-of-sylva.html">Check It Out</a></b></p>]]>
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Clanime - Happy Time Ranger Super Lasty Show</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/sticklordblog/2008/06/clanime.html" />
    <id>tag:sticklord.com,2009:/sticklordblog//2.226</id>

    <published>2008-06-08T04:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2009-04-27T03:10:50Z</updated>

    <summary>A special message from StickLord mastermind Hoggle: This is a short I did entirely in the free animation application Pencil with compositing done in Shake. It is basically having fun with the anime genre with a huge nod to Inuyasha....</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Bi-ru the Wonder Hamster</name>
    </author>

    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us" xml:base="/sticklordblog/">
        <![CDATA[<p>A special message from StickLord mastermind Hoggle:</p>

<p><i>This is a short I did entirely in the free animation application <a href="http://www.les-stooges.org/pascal/pencil/index.php">Pencil</a> with compositing done in <a href="https://www.apple.com/shake/">Shake</a>. It is basically having fun with the anime genre with a huge nod to <i>Inuyasha</i>. The characters are players in the MMORPG <a href="http://clanlord.com">Clan Lord</a> (Check out the <a href="http://www.deltatao.com/clanlord/demo.html">free demo</a>!)</p>

<p>This is me pushing Pencil as far as my skills are currently able to. If you are interested in animation be sure to <a href="http://www.les-stooges.org/pascal/pencil/index.php">check it out</a>. I want to give a HUGE thanks to Rina-chan for her voicework. Rina-chan and other excellent voice actor/actresses can be found at <a href="http://voiceacting.proboards62.com/index.cgi">the Voice Acting Club</a> &mdash; I highly recommend them as a great resource for your animation voicing needs. Also, a final thanks to Skirwan for his awesome webpagery and little ideas (such as Bi-ru!) that seem to find their way into several of my animations.</i></p>]]>
        
<![CDATA[<p><b><a href="/sticklordblog/2008/06/clanime.html">Check It Out</a></b></p>]]>
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>SNN: Phroon Thoom Reporting</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/sticklordblog/2007/05/snn-phroon-thoom-reporting.html" />
    <id>tag:sticklord.com,2009:/sticklordblog//2.225</id>

    <published>2007-05-07T04:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2009-04-27T02:30:00Z</updated>

    <summary>This landmark episode introduced T&apos;rool Ambassador Gaak, found one of the most popular StickLord characters ever in an informal poll of the person writing this summary. Fans have called him StickLord&apos;s Boba Fett, alluding to a character in the cult-classic...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Bi-ru the Wonder Hamster</name>
    </author>

    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us" xml:base="/sticklordblog/">
        <![CDATA[<p>This landmark episode introduced T'rool Ambassador Gaak, found one of the most popular StickLord characters ever in an informal poll of the person writing this summary.  Fans have called him StickLord's Boba Fett, alluding to a character in the cult-classic StickLord parody 'Star Wars' that went on to be far more popular than the primary protagonists.</p>

<p>Fun Fact: The only characters to appear in every SNN broadcast are Phroon and R2D2.</p>

<p>If you didn't notice Phroon in the Planar Warming PSA, that's because you're blind.  Your mother and I have been discussing how to break the news to you.  She wanted to print it on a slip of paper and hide it in a fortune cookie the next time we had Chinese, but I pointed out to her that that was a somewhat insensitive way of telling you and besides you wouldn't be able to read it because you're frakking <i>blind</i>.  So now you know.</p>]]>
        
<![CDATA[<p><b><a href="/sticklordblog/2007/05/snn-phroon-thoom-reporting.html">Check It Out</a></b></p>]]>
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>The More You Zo: A Planar Warning</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/sticklordblog/2007/02/snn-a-planar-warning.html" />
    <id>tag:sticklord.com,2009:/sticklordblog//2.222</id>

    <published>2007-02-14T05:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2009-04-27T00:28:27Z</updated>

    <summary>Throughout the mid-540s the StickLord News Network produced a series of public-service announcements under the tag line &apos;The More You Zo&apos; featuring Zo celebrities from its various properties. Though that timeline has since been extensively altered following a severe temporal...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Bi-ru the Wonder Hamster</name>
    </author>

    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us" xml:base="/sticklordblog/">
        <![CDATA[<p>Throughout the mid-540s the StickLord News Network produced a series of public-service announcements under the tag line 'The More You Zo' featuring Zo celebrities from its various properties.  Though that timeline has since been extensively altered following a severe temporal incident involving a stuffed tiger and an un-pressed button, this example was preserved by a kindly higher-dimensional sentient shade of the color blue.</p>

<p>Planar warming was a severe issue in Puddleby in the timeline during which this piece was produced, leading in fact to the eventual destruction of that plane and, indirectly through various means, to the financial crisis plaguing Puddleby in this continuity  (see also: 'Alliance Castle Bailout').</p>]]>
        
<![CDATA[<p><b><a href="/sticklordblog/2007/02/snn-a-planar-warning.html">Check It Out</a></b></p>]]>
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Episode 3: Revenge of the Slyph</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/sticklordblog/2006/10/episode-3-revenge-of-the-slyph.html" />
    <id>tag:sticklord.com,2006:/sticklordblog//2.224</id>

    <published>2006-10-30T05:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2009-04-27T02:54:13Z</updated>

    <summary> The third and final installment in the classic StickLord trilogy, Revenge of the Slyph (released internationally as Zynx&apos;s Day Out) was written and filmed by StickLord newcomes the Wachowski brothers. It was released simultaneously in sixty countries on October...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Bi-ru the Wonder Hamster</name>
    </author>

    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us" xml:base="/sticklordblog/">
        <![CDATA[<p> The third and final installment in the classic StickLord trilogy, <i>Revenge of the Slyph</i> (released internationally as <i>Zynx's Day Out</i>) was written and filmed by StickLord newcomes the Wachowski brothers.  It was released simultaneously in sixty countries on October 30, 2006, and was the second live-action film to be released in both regular and IMAX movie theaters at the same time.</p>

<p>Critical reception was mixed; though it was regarded as less philosophically ambiguous than its predecessor, the complex moral and ethical themes explored throughout the series were brought to a powerful head here in the apocalyptic final battle between Sleipnir and the army of Zynx clones.  Many felt the film demonstrated an alarming degree of self-indulgence in exploring themes in a fashion that many viewers found opaque and inscrutable.</p>]]>
        
<![CDATA[<p><b><a href="/sticklordblog/2006/10/episode-3-revenge-of-the-slyph.html">Check It Out</a></b></p>]]>
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Episode 2: Attack of the Orga</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/sticklordblog/2006/09/episode-2-attack-of-the-orga.html" />
    <id>tag:sticklord.com,2009:/sticklordblog//2.223</id>

    <published>2006-09-30T04:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2009-04-27T00:02:12Z</updated>

    <summary>Following a difficult production, Attack of the Orga was released on September 30, 2006, and received mixed reviews from critics, though it has since grown in esteem to become one of the most well-regarded chapters of the saga and one...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Bi-ru the Wonder Hamster</name>
    </author>

    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us" xml:base="/sticklordblog/">
        <![CDATA[<p>Following a difficult production, <i>Attack of the Orga</i> was released on September 30, 2006, and received mixed reviews from critics, though it has since grown in esteem to become one of the most well-regarded chapters of the saga and one of the most highly rated films in history.</p>

<p>Though it has never been explicitly acknowledged, it is considered an 'open secret' amongst StickLord aficionados that Episode 2 was not in fact the second StickLord episode produced.  Rather, <i>Attack of the Orga</i> was produced at approximately the same time as the original SNN production run and retroactively inserted into the memory of every living person sometime in late 2008 using a powerful spell.</p>

<p>The memory-modification spell was in fact so powerful that it incidentally resulted in the destruction of Lunus, the Earth's second moon.  Faced with this accidental destruction, the StickLord production mages chose to perform a second, even more powerful spell to eradicate all human memory of Lunus.  Though this spell performed as intended, it had the unintended side effect of erasing the island civilization of Atlantis from history and severely disrupting all memory of the same.</p>

<p>Savvy StickLord fans have since realized that this memory-modification debacle can be useful in detecting the undead; as only living beings were affected by the alteration, beings that were dead at the time but have since risen will reveal themselves in the belief that Episode 3 was produced prior to Episode 2, that the Earth has a second moon, and that Atlantis existed.</p>

<p>Time-traveling StickLord fans working as writers on the television series <i>Angel</i> in 2003 used this factoid as the basis for a brief plot arc in season four of the hit series.</p>]]>
        
<![CDATA[<p><b><a href="/sticklordblog/2006/09/episode-2-attack-of-the-orga.html">Check It Out</a></b></p>]]>
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Episode 1: Tanks 4 U</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/sticklordblog/2006/09/episode-1-tanks-4-u.html" />
    <id>tag:sticklord.com,2009:/sticklordblog//2.221</id>

    <published>2006-09-08T04:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2009-04-27T00:00:38Z</updated>

    <summary>The critically-acclaimed animated classic that started it all. Originally released as simply &apos;Tanks 4 U&apos;, the full title was expanded to &apos;StickLord Episode 1: Tanks 4 U&apos; following the release of the sequel and the reissue of the original on...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Bi-ru the Wonder Hamster</name>
    </author>

    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us" xml:base="/sticklordblog/">
        <![CDATA[<p>The critically-acclaimed animated classic that started it all.</p>

<p>Originally released as simply 'Tanks 4 U', the full title was expanded to 'StickLord Episode 1: Tanks 4 U' following the release of the sequel and the reissue of the original on high-definition HD cassette tape.  'T4U', as StickLord fans have affectionately nicknamed the piece, provided the world its first introduction to the StickLord universe, a glimpse that would inspire the sale of millions of dollars' worth of home videos, clothing, and toy merchandise.</p>

<p>As the original print of T4U was stolen by a time-traveling cybernetic chicken in 1947 following the second robot civil war in a since-aborted timeline, the only remaining record of this classic feat of cinema is a poor-quality YouTube transcription.  StickLord Media Interplanar licenses the video to Google for the nominal sum of $1 Canadian per year to ensure that this outstanding film remains accessible for generations to come.</p>]]>
        
<![CDATA[<p><b><a href="/sticklordblog/2006/09/episode-1-tanks-4-u.html">Check It Out</a></b></p>]]>
    </content>
</entry>

</feed>
